Guide to the Jobs With Justice Records 2001-2012
Jobs With Justice Records
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Jobs With Justice Records, 2001-2012
6369
Jobs With Justice
41 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Jobs with Justice (JWJ) is a non-profit workers' advocacy organization based in Washington, D.C. Marking its beginning with a convening in Miami in 1987, JWJ started with members pledging to support others' fights for economic justice, as well as their own. Since that time, Jobs with Justice has grown to forty-five local affiliations in twenty-four states across the United States, and members now pledge to "stand up for our rights as working people to a decent standard of living; support the rights of all workers to organize and bargain collectively; fight for secure family-wage jobs in the face of corporate attacks on working people and our communities; organize the unorganized to take aggressive action to secure a better economic future for all of us; and mobilize those already organized to join the fight for jobs with justice" (http://www.jwj.org/about-us/our- history, accessed 2/7/14).
Jobs with Justice organizes across community lines, working with community, student, faith, and organized labor groups. Significant JWJ campaigns include the Justice for Janitors (1985), Justice at Verizon (1989), Justice at Smithfield (2008).
Communications Workers of America (CWA) President Larry Cohen founded Jobs with Justice in 1987. Since 2007, Sarita Gupta has served as Jobs with Justice's Executive Director. In 2012, American Rights at Work and Jobs with Justice merged.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
6369 AV: Jobs With Justice Audio-Visual Materials
6369 MB: Jobs With Justice Memorabilia
6369 P: Jobs With Justice Photographs
CONTAINER LIST
- A1: Planning and Tracking (Box 1)
  - Steering Committee Mailings, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee Mailings, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Key and Steering Committee Mailings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Key List Mailing, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Presidents' Council Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Presidents' Council Packets, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    April 1999
  - Presidents' Council Mailing, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Tracking, DB, Out, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Documentation of Union Campaigns, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tracking, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - IUOE, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - IUPAT, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Laborers International Union (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - LIUNA, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    April - February 2002
  - National Organization of Legal Services Workers, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    March 31 1995
  - PACE: Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - PCUN, Farmworkers Union, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Roofers and Waterproofers, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    May 2002
  - Service Employees International Union, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - SEIU, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - IBT, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Temporary Workers Union, Cleveland, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - United Auto Workers, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    January - February 2002
  - Unions, United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - National Farmers Union, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - UMWA Journal, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - UNITE, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - UE Convention (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - UE Convention, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - UFCW, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - USWA, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Support Tejano Advancement in Recording, AFM, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - AFSCME, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - AFT, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - APWU, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ATO, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CWA, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Unions, CWA Organizing Manual, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    October 1987
  - CWA, Talking Union (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - CWA, Missouri State Workers Union, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    January 21 1999
  - "Membership-Based Organizing Vs. the Mobile Organizer Model: Worker Employment is the Way to Win" (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Steve Early
  - Hotel Employees Restaurant Employees, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    January 1998
  - HERE, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - IAM, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    February - May 2002
  - IBEW, 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Teamster Updates, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - AFT, Teacher, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - AFSCME, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - ATJ, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Carpenters, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    English and Spanish
  - CWA, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - HERE, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - PACE, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    October and November 2002
  - IBT, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - ILWU, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Laborers, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Spanish and English
  - UAW, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - UNITE, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - SEIU, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    English and French
  - UE, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - UFCW, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - USWA, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Emails and Union Tracking Forms, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Emails and Union Tracking Forms II, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Emails and Union Tracking Forms III, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- A2: Planning and Tracking; Union Files (Box 2)
  - First Folder (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Jobs with Justice Starter Kit (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jobs with Justice Structure, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Committee, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jobs with Justice Affiliation Agreement (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Jobs with Justice AFL-CIO Proposal, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jobs with Justice History, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local Coalition Calls, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local Coalition Contacts, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local Coalition Builders, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local Coalition Building, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Local Coalition Building, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Jobs with Justice Coalition Reports, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    February 27 1996
  - Jobs with Justice Event and Media Reports, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Local Coalitions Survey, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Local Coalitions Survey, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - National Steering Committee and Miscellaneous Documents, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Staff Retreat, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    December 1999
  - Local Planning Retreats, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Tracking History, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Workers' Rights Board, 1994-2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Jobs with Justice, Worker's Rights Board, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Workers' Rights Board Mailings, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Workers' Rights Board Conference Call, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board Advising Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Workers' Rights Board Advising Committee Mailing, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Jobs with Justice Workers' Rights Board Stories, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Coordinating Meeting, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Coordinating Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Steering Committee Meetings 1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    August 1987
  - Presidents' Council Meeting, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Presidents' Council meetings, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Presidents' Council Meeting, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    January 1994
  - Presidents' Council Meeting, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Presidents' Council meetings, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - President's Council Mailing, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    February 1998
  - President's Council, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    September 1997
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Presidents Council Meeting, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    February 28 1996
  - Presidents Council 1998 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Jobs with Justice Steering Committee Meeting, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    November 5 1999
  - Steering Committee Attendance, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Steering Committee, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    December 1998
  - Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    September 1998
  - Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    July 1998
  - Steering Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    April 1998
  - Steering Committee, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Steering Committee Meetings, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - National Steering Committee Meetings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    July 14 1997
  - Steering Committee Mailings, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- B1: Mailings; Press Clips; SLAP (Box 3)
  - Press Clips, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Press Clips, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Press Clips, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - FTAA Press Clips, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Alphabetical by paper
  - Press Clips, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Press Clips, Photos, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Labels, FEB Mailing, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - February Monthly Mailing, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Jobs with Justice Lexis Search, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Press Clips, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Press Clips, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Press Clips, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Press Clips, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Jobs with Justice Press Releases, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - May Originals, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - April Mailing, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Labor Mailings, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - March Originals, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Press Clips, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    April 4 2002
  - Local Action Materials, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    April 4 2001
  - Newsletter, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Winter 2005
  - Winter 2004 Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Spring, Summer 2002 Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fall 2002, Winter 2003 Newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Spring 2001 Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Winter 1999 Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jobs with Justice 1998 Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- B1.5: Mailing; Press Clips; SLAP (Box 4)
  - Event Report Forms, Jobs with Justice, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    November 26 1997
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Communications Survey, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter and Clippings, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    August 2000
  - Monthly Mailing, May, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Update, May 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - November Mailing, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - October Mailing Originals, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Workers' Rights Board Member Mailing, October 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Jobs with Justice Miscellaneous, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - National Staff Report, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Jobs with Justice Annual Report, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - July Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Coalition Mailings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Coalition Mailings, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Coalition Mailings, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - June Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Coalition Mailings, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Coalition Mailings, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - May Mailing No. 2, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - May Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - April Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Old Newsletters, 1996-1999 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - February Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Coalition Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    January 8 1997
  - Originals, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - UPS, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Originals for August 1997 Mailing (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - March Mailing, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - September Mailing, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - August Mailing Originals, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - January 1999 Mailing (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - January Mailing, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Originals, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - July Originals, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- B2: Newsletters; Monthly Updates (Box 5)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters 1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Early Jobs with Justice Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Jobs with Justice: A Strategic Approach to the New Economy, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    February 2001
  - Jobs with Justice "En Espanol" (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Spanish
  - "Jobs Justice Joy" Article, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    March 22 1999
  - Modern Healthcare, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - NJ Public Worker Ad (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Grinch Parties, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Press Clips 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Early 2000's Press Clips, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Press Clips, Early 2000's, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Haitian Nursing Home Workers, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting Follow-Up Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Jobs with Justice Press Clips and "Social Policy", 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Press Items About Labor I, 2005-2011 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Press Items about Labor II, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - National Press, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - National and regional Press, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - National Press and Regional Healthcare Press, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - National Press, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - National Press and Regional Economic Development Press, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - National Press and Regional Immigration, Other Press, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - National and Regional Press Miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - SLACtivist 2004 Winter, Spring (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - SLAP Week of Action 2004 Highlights (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - SLAP Week of Action Clips 2004 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - SLACtivist Fall, Winter 2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - SLACtivist Summer, Fall 2001 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - SLAP Day of Action 2002 Highlights (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Workers' Rights Board Update Spring 2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Workers' Rights Board Update Fall 2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - SLACtivist Winter, Spring 2002 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - SLAP Day of Action 2001 Highlights (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - SLAP Week of Action 2003 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Summer 2005 WORKERS' Rights Board Update (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Jobs with Justice Update February 2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Updates and Press Clips, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    January and February 2005
  - Summer 2004 Workers' Rights Board Update (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - SLACtivist Winter, Spring 2004 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Jobs with Justice Updates and Press Clips, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    May 2004
  - September - October 2004 Update (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Update June-July 2004 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - April 2004 Updates and Press Clips (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Jobs with Justice Updates March 2004 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Press Clips January 2004 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - December Workers' Rights Board Updates and Press Clips, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Jobs with Justice Year in Media, For Board, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - December 10 (D10) Report 2003 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Fall 2003 Workers' Rights Board Update (Box 5, Folder 50)
- B3: Monthly Updates 1999-2003 (Box 6)
  - November 2003 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - September 2003 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - August 2003 Mailings (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - May-July Mailings, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - April 2003 Press (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - March 2003 "It Takes a Community" (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - January 2003 Updates and Press (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - November 2002 Emails and Press (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - October 2002 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - September 2002 Mailing (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - August 2002 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - July 2002 Mailings (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - June 2002 Mailings (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - May 2002 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - March 2002 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - February 2002 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - January 2002 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - December 2001 Mailings (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - November 2001 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - October 2001 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - August 2001 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - July 2001 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - May 2001 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - February 2001 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - January - February 2001 Mailings (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - November 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - October 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - September 2000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - August 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - March 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - April 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - February 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - January 2000 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - October 1999 Mailings (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - September 1999 Mailing (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - August 1999 Mailing (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - November 1999 Mailings and Press (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - June 1999 Monthly Mailing (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - May Mailing 1999 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - April 1999 Mailing (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - March 1999 Workers' Rights Board Member Mailing Originals (Box 6, Folder 41)
- B4: Monthly Updates 1999-2003; Print Materials 1997-2009; Materials Research (Box 7)
  - March 1999 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - January 1999 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - July 1998 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - August 1998 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - January and February 1998 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - July 1997 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - April 1997 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - May 1997 Mailing (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1997 Conference Book (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Workers Rights Directory 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Workers Rights Directory 2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Workers Rights Directory 2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Workers Rights Directory 2006 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Resources for Faith-Based Activists, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Comics "The Big Fix" on Right to Organize (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Approximately 1997-1999
  - FTAA Educational, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Workers Rights, Communities' Fights, Workers' Rights Boards, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    September 9 2001
  - MLK Quote Cards (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Assorted Postcards, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Old Publications, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Assorted Brochures, Early Days (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Assorted Pledge Cards, Ballots, etc., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 2003 Annual Meeting, Brochure, Conference (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 2005 Annual Meeting Brochure (Conference) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 2009 Economic Meltdown Funnies (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Healthcare Action Toolkit 2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Verizon Campaign Organizing Kit (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Year Unknown, after 2008
  - Immigrant Workers' Freedom Ride Student Organization Kit, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - SLAP Day of Action 4-Pager, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Campus Living Wage Manual (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - SLAP Day of Action 4-Pager, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - SLAP Week of Action 4-Pager, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - SLAP Week of Action 4-Pager, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Immigrant Worker Freedom Ride 4-Pager, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Kentucky-Sonora Worker Exchange, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - FTAA 4-Pager, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Workers' Rights are Human Rights Educational, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - FTAA 4-Pager, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Healthcare 4 All 4-Pager, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Right to Organize 4-Pager, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Annual Meeting, Conference 4-Pager Brochure, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - S26 4-Pager, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    September 26 2000
  - Welfare Reform Comic (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Workers Rights Board Reports, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Boston Globe, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Chicago Tribune, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Los Angeles Times, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - NY Times, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    February 10 2005
  - Philadelphia Inquirer, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    May 6 2005
  - Washington Post, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    February 17 and 18 2005
  - Other, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Wires, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    February 17 2005
  - Columnists and Editors, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    February 2005
  - Economic Development, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    June 2004
  - Regional Media Contacts, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Healthcare, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Immigrant Rights, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - OCBR, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Social Security, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    January 20 2005
  - Wal-Mart, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - OCBR Training, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - SLAP Week of Action, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - SLAP Week of Action 2006 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Labor Press and Reports, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- B5: Regional Press Clippings; Misc. Print Materials; JWJ Early Years 1987 - (Box 8)
  - Economic Development, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Healthcare, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Immigrant Rights in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - OCBR in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Economic Development in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Global Justice in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Healthcare in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Immigrant Rights in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - OCBR in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Economic development in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Immigrant Rights in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Economic Development in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Global Justice in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Immigrant Rights in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - OCBR in order, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Local Coalition Support (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Voice at Work, Freedom to Choose a Union, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - American Rights at Work, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Press Associates Union News Service, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Unsolicited Media Call Intake Forms, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Pitch Response Forms, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - World Economic Forum, World Social Forum, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - State Budget Crisis (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Colombia, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Jobs with Justice, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Miami, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Jobs with Justice, Miami, Labor Day, Press Clippings, Steering Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Early Papers, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Jobs with Justice Success Stories, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Early Papers, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Press Clips, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Jobs with Justice Information 1980's - 1990's, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Labor Day 1988 (Box 8, Folder 35)